freesprinkles.com 2015-03-14

# Privacy Policy | Free Sprinkles

Freesprinkles.com is a website for original and curated photos and videos.

Your personal privacy is very important to us. The following policy explains how we collect, protect and use your personal identifying information. Please read this policy carefully, and if you have any questions, contact us at your convenience.

By using Freesprinkles.com, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. We may update this privacy policy as we see fit and will post a notice of significant changes on the site. We invite you to visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the policy.

**The information we collect**  
We only collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, submission form or other direct contact from you. This includes your name, email address, and potentially hometown, state and country. When you upload a video you created or recommended, we collect only the information you choose to share about that video. Your name and email will never be shared, rented, bartered or sold with other users or third-party companies. The information you share with us about your video(s) will only be used by Freesprinkles.com for display and informational purposes on our site, and will never be shared, rented, bartered, sold or exchanged any other purposeful manner.

Unless you request us not to, we may email you in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this policy.

The website, however, can be accessed by anyone with an internet connection and a web browser; as such, any information, photos or videos you post can be copied by any other internet user.

In order to provide you with the best possible experience and identify and correct site errors, we collect aggregate information about use of our site (such as most often viewed pages), and we collect information about your computer, such as such as browser type, browser language, and IP address. We do not share this information with anyone.

**How we use your information**  
You have complete control over the information you submit to our site. You may edit this information or request to have your personal account removed entirely at any time. We reserve the right to transfer your submitted information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Freesprinkles.com, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, Freesprinkles.com will notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We work with third parties who provide administrative services, including website hosting, e-commerce affiliation, data analysis, emailing and other services. Personally identifiable information is shared with these third parties in order for them to provide such services. Further, we may work with reputable third parties for marketing, targeting and analysis purposes. Some of these third parties may be given access to some or all of the information that you provide to us and may use cookies or other tracking technologies in connection with providing their services. To the extent that we provide your personally identifiable information to such third parties, we will attempt to restrict their ability to use your information for their own marketing purposes; however, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such third parties.

The information, photos and videos you enter are available to all users of the site as soon as they are published. Freesprinkles.com claims no rights over the photos or videos you upload or the information you add to the site. Please note, however, that this is a public site, so any information you provide is available to anyone with internet access. As such, so you should never post a photo or fact that you do not now or ever want to share on a public site.

**Your Access to and Control Over Your Information**  
You can opt out of any future contact from us at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number listed on our site.

**Security  ** **  
** In case we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), it is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. This is verified by the closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or the “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

**Legal requests**  
You understand and consent to the fact that Freesprinkles.com may access, preserve and disclose your personal information and the contents of your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect the rights and property of Freesprinkles.com, its affiliates or the public.

**Cookies**  
We send “cookies” to your computer and use them to improve the quality and ease of use of our service for our members. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. We store user preferences in cookies and track user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of this site may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

**External links**  
Freesprinkles.com contains links to other web sites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information.

**Security**  
We use industry-standard security measures to protect your information so that it is not made available to unauthorized parties. If you have any questions regarding these measures and techniques, please contact us.

**Contacting Us**  
You can always contact us at any time through [this form](mailto:http://freesprinkles.com/contact/).

**Unsubscribing**  
You can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the footer of the email you receive from us. Clicking on that link will take you immediately to a page where you can unsubscribe or opt-out from all email correspondence from Freesprinkles.com.

**Payments**  
All payments made via Freesprinkles.com are encrypted using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology. Your credit card information is passed securely to our credit card processor but is not stored on our servers. Freesprinkles.com’s employees do not have access to your credit card information.

**Log Files**  
We collect and use data contained in log files, including your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Chrome), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Affiliate Disclosure**  
Links to products on this website may generate an affiliate commission for Freesprinkles.com. We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

You can chose to disable or turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs like Norton Internet Security. However, disabling cookies may affect how you interact with our site as well as other websites, including the inability to log in to services, forums or accounts.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately using[this form](http://freesprinkles.com/contact/).**
